more than a decade, I worked
my guts out and I was
always stressed out because I was
doing it all. And I would
let certain people do things, but
I'd always upset, criticized. They didn't
do it well. And so I
was trapped. I was in the
founder's trap. In that trap, you
can't grow because there's no leverage.
The only way out of it
is to start developing some people.
Success in business, in life is
the result of one thing, good
judgment. You make good decisions, you're
going to crush it. Now the
problem is, are you always going
to make good decisions? Are the
people you hire who are maybe
not yet as skilled or talented
in this area as you, are
they going to make bad decisions?
Yes, and most of your good
decisions came because good decisions are
the result of experience. Experience is
often the result of bad decisions.
So you have to have them
be able to fail and still
support or you'll never have a
business. if you can learn faster
than other people, and you can
if you recognize patterns, learn to
use them, you do that, you'll
dominate. If you try not to
make a mistake, it's already over
for you because the tempo will
not allow you to go without
making a mistake. And let me
give you the rules of